YASMINE SAAD

OBJECTIVE

My goal is to incorporate my acquired experience and international background to advise others with a different perspective. I have a passion to help others around me with mastering their craft and becoming a better version of themselves.

EDUCATION

BALDWIN WALLACE UNIVERSITY - BEREA, OHIO

BACHELOR OF ARTS

- Major: International Studies
- Minor: Economics
 - ⇒ <u>Courses Include</u>: U.S. Government and Politics, Labor Economics, Statistics, International Politics, Business Ethics, and America in the World
 - ⇒ Academic Honors: Dean's list

EXPERIENCE

QUICKEN LOANS

September 9, 2019 - Present

Power Banker

- Advised clients on the home buying process
- Assisted clients through the loan process from application to closing
- Actively worked to provide an excellent client experience
- Collaborated with team members to achieve monthly goals and increase production

ANGEL DENTAL CARE

March 2018 - August 2019

Office Receptionist

- Responsible over providing translation for all Arabic speaking patients
- · Responsible in creating and organizing the doctor's daily schedule
- Responsible over daily communication with insurances on behalf of the office and its patients
- Helped create a organization system for daily office procedures

THE AMERICAN INTERNATIONAL SCHOOL - CAIRO, EGYPT

May 2017 - August 2017

Assistant

- Advised high school students on their concerns regarding university
- Worked closely with the Economics and Global Politics teachers to manage and maintain a positive class environment
- Worked closely teachers to create new methods of learning for the students to help maintain engagement

UNITED NATIONS DEVELOPMENT PROGRAMME - CAIRO, EGYPT

May 2016 - August 2016

Poverty Reduction Intern

- Participated in the "Egypt Network for Integrated Development (ENID)" project
- Collaborated with fellow employees to ensure that the Egyptian government continued to provide funding for the ENID project

RED BULL - CAIRO, EGYPT

May 2015 - January 2016

Red Bull Associate

- Became an effective first line of communication between Red Bull and the public
- Assisted in the activation and management of Red Bull's "Summer Mania" in Egypt
- Regarded as the face of the brand and was responsible in spreading awareness of Red Bull's mission

SKILLS

- Bilingual with near-native fluency in Arabic
- Proficient in Microsoft Word, Excel, and PowerPoint